(Steph:)So we're all standing around
looking at the post-op X-ray...
(Steph:)...and there it is, clear as day,
right in the guy's chest cavity:
(Steph:)One of my earrings.
(Leonard:)Oh, my God, what did you do?
Ha, ha. What do you think I did?
(Steph:)I discreetly slipped off the other earring...
(Steph:)...put it in my pocket,
and then got the hell out of there.
[LAUGHS]
- I have a bone to pick with you, sir.
- Oh!
- Hi, Sheldon.
- Hi, Stephanie.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry I'm late, but your companion
left the most indecipherable invitation.
(Leonard:)What invitation?
"We're going to the movies."
What movie? What theater? What time?
(Sheldon:)If you were trying to make it impossible to
locate you, you couldn't have done better.
(Leonard:)Oh, clearly, I could have.
It took 20 minutes to go through...
(Sheldon:)...the browser history on your computer
to see what movie times you looked up.